Public Sub SC_Merge()
Public Sub SC_CopyVisible()
Public Sub SC_SelectVisible()
Private Sub Workbook_Open()
Private Sub Workbook_BeforeClose(Cancel As Boolean)
Private Sub CreateMenu()
Private Sub DeleteMenu()


Public Function Series_ScatterplotUpdate(ChartName As String, SeriesName As String, XRange As Range, YRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Series_LineUpdate(ChartName As String, SeriesName As String, YRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function PrintChartAddress(thisRange As Range) As Variant
Private Sub CachChart()
Private Sub EachChartObject()



Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_popen Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "popen" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_pclose Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "pclose" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_fread Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "fread" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_feof Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "feof" _
Private Declare Function utc_popen Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "popen" _
Private Declare Function utc_pclose Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "pclose" _
Private Declare Function utc_fread Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "fread" _
Private Declare Function utc_feof Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "feof" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_GetTimeZoneInformation Lib "kernel32" Alias "GetTimeZoneInformation" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime" _
Private Declare Function utc_GetTimeZoneInformation Lib "kernel32" Alias "GetTimeZoneInformation" _
Private Declare Function utc_SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime" _
Private Declare Function utc_TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime" _



Public Function ParseJson(ByVal JsonString As String) As Object
Public Function ConvertToJson(ByVal JsonValue As Variant, Optional ByVal Whitespace As Variant, Optional ByVal json_CurrentIndentation As Long = 0) As String
Private Declare PtrSafe Sub json_CopyMemory Lib "kernel32" Alias "RtlMoveMemory" _
Private Declare Sub json_CopyMemory Lib "kernel32" Alias "RtlMoveMemory" _
Private Sub json_SkipSpaces(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long)
Private Sub json_BufferAppend(ByRef json_buffer As String, _
Private Function json_ParseObject(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As Dictionary
Private Function json_ParseArray(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As Collection
Private Function json_ParseValue(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As Variant
Private Function json_ParseString(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As String
Private Function json_ParseNumber(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As Variant
Private Function json_ParseKey(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long) As String
Private Function json_IsUndefined(ByVal json_Value As Variant) As Boolean
Private Function json_Encode(ByVal json_Text As Variant) As String
Private Function json_Peek(json_String As String, ByVal json_Index As Long, Optional json_NumberOfCharacters As Long = 1) As String
Private Function json_StringIsLargeNumber(json_String As Variant) As Boolean
Private Function json_ParseErrorMessage(json_String As String, ByRef json_Index As Long, ErrorMessage As String)
Private Function json_BufferToString(ByRef json_buffer As String, ByVal json_BufferPosition As Long, ByVal json_BufferLength As Long) As String
Private Function json_UnsignedAdd(json_Start As LongPtr, json_Increment As Long) As LongPtr
Private Function json_UnsignedAdd(json_Start As Long, json_Increment As Long) As Long



Public Function ParseUtc(utc_UtcDate As Date) As Date
Public Function ConvertToUtc(utc_LocalDate As Date) As Date
Public Function ParseIso(utc_IsoString As String) As Date
Public Function ConvertToIso(utc_LocalDate As Date) As String
Private Function utc_ConvertDate(utc_Value As Date, Optional utc_ConvertToUtc As Boolean = False) As Date
Private Function utc_ExecuteInShell(utc_ShellCommand As String) As utc_ShellResult
Private Function utc_DateToSystemTime(utc_Value As Date) As utc_SYSTEMTIME
Private Function utc_SystemTimeToDate(utc_Value As utc_SYSTEMTIME) As Date


Public Sub run()
Public Sub run_WithDecimals()
Public Sub ConvertTextToNumber(ByVal cell As Range)
Public Sub ConvertTextToNumber_WithDecimals(ByVal cell As Range)
Public Function convertTextToNumber_CountDecimals(ByVal cell As Range) As Integer
Public Function convertTextToNumber_GetCurrentDisplay(ByVal cell As Range) As String
Public Function convertTextToNumber_DashToZero(ByVal val As String) As Double
Public Function convertTextToNumber_Parenthesis(ByVal val As String) As Double
Public Function convertTextToNumber_DeleteSeparators(ByVal val As String) As String
Public Function convertTextToNumber_AddDecimals(ByVal val As Double, Optional ByVal numberDecimals As Variant) As Double
Public Sub convertDecimalSeparator()
Public Sub ChangeSystemSeparators()

Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_popen Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "popen" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_pclose Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "pclose" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_fread Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "fread" _
Private Declare PtrSafe Function utc_feof Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "feof" _
Private Declare Function utc_popen Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "popen" _
Private Declare Function utc_pclose Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "pclose" _
Private Declare Function utc_fread Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "fread" _
Private Declare Function utc_feof Lib "libc.dylib" Alias "feof" _
Private Declare Function utc_GetTimeZoneInformation Lib "kernel32" Alias "GetTimeZoneInformation" _
Private Declare Function utc_SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "SystemTimeToTzSpecificLocalTime" _
Private Declare Function utc_TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime Lib "kernel32" Alias "TzSpecificLocalTimeToSystemTime" _



Private Function utc_ConvertDate(utc_Value As Date, Optional utc_ConvertToUtc As Boolean = False) As Date
Private Function utc_ExecuteInShell(utc_ShellCommand As String) As utc_ShellResult
Private Function utc_DateToSystemTime(utc_Value As Date) As utc_SYSTEMTIME
Private Function utc_SystemTimeToDate(utc_Value As utc_SYSTEMTIME) As Date
Private Declare PtrSafe Sub json_CopyMemory Lib "kernel32" Alias "RtlMoveMemory" _



Public Function ParseXml(ByVal xml_String As String) As Dictionary
Public Function ConvertToXML(ByVal xml_Dictionary As Dictionary) As String
Private Sub xml_SkipSpaces(xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long)
Private Sub xml_BufferAppend(ByRef xml_buffer As String, _
*Private Declare Sub json_CopyMemory Lib "kernel32" Alias "RtlMoveMemory" _
Private Function xml_ParseProlog(xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long) As String
Private Function xml_ParseDoctype(xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long) As String
Private Function xml_ParseNode(xml_Parent As Dictionary, xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long) As Dictionary
Private Function xml_ParseAttributes(ByRef xml_Node As Dictionary, xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long) As Collection
Private Function xml_ParseChildNodes(ByRef xml_Node As Dictionary, xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long) As Collection
Private Function xml_IsVoidNode(xml_Node As Dictionary) As Boolean
Private Function xml_ProcessString(xml_String As String) As String
Private Function xml_RootNode(xml_Node As Dictionary) As Dictionary
Private Function xml_StringIsLargeNumber(xml_String As Variant) As Boolean
Private Function xml_ParseErrorMessage(xml_String As String, ByRef xml_Index As Long, xml_ErrorMessage As String)
Private Function xml_BufferToString(ByRef xml_buffer As String, ByVal xml_BufferPosition As Long, ByVal xml_BufferLength As Long) As String
Private Function xml_UnsignedAdd(xml_Start As LongPtr, xml_Increment As Long) As LongPtr
Private Function xml_UnsignedAdd(xml_Start As Long, xml_Increment As Long) As Long






Public Sub ImportExcelSheets(sheetsSpec() As Variant, Optional wb As Workbook)
Public Function ExportExcelSheets(sheetsSpec() As Variant, _
Private Sub CopyExcelSheets(wb As Workbook, sheetsSpec() As Variant, allowThisWorkbook As Boolean)

Public Function SelectNewOrExistingFile(Optional FileType As FileTypes = 0, Optional MenuTitleName = "Select File", Optional StartingPath = "WBPath", Optional CustomFilter As String = "Any File (*.*), *.*") As Variant
Public Function SelectExistingFolder(Optional MenuTitleName As String = "Select Folder", Optional ByVal StartingPath As String = "WBPath") As Variant
Public Function SelectExistingFile(Optional FileType As FileTypes = 0, Optional MenuTitleName = "Select File", Optional StartingPath = "WBPath", Optional CustomFilter As String = "Any File (*.*), *.*") As Variant
Private Function GetCustomFilterList(FileTypeNumber As FileTypes, CustomFilter As String) As Variant

Public Function MakeDirString(PathString As String) As Variant
Public Function MakeDirFullPath(Path As String) As Boolean

Public Function FileListInFolder(ByVal PathName As String, Optional ByVal FileFilter As String = "*.*") As Collection
Public Function GetFileInfo(FN As String, FileInfo As GetFileInfo, Optional ShowErrorPopup As Boolean = False) As Variant

Private Function DoesFileExist(FN As String) As Variant
Public Function IsValidFileName(FN As String) As Boolean
Public Function IsFileOpen(FN As String) As Variant

Public Function Kill2(ByVal PathName As String) As Boolean
Public Function FileCopy2(ByVal SourceFile As String, ByVal DestinationFile As String) As Boolean

Function FileExists(ByVal strFile As String, Optional bFindFolders As Boolean) As Boolean
Public Sub CopyFileBypassErr(Src As String, des As String)
Public Function ExtractZipInDir(SrcDir As String, DesDir As String, Optional Criteria As String = "", Optional DeleteZipFile As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function ExtractZip(Src As String, DesDir As String, Optional DeleteZipFile As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function FTPUpload(Site, sUsername, sPassword, sLocalFile, sRemotePath, Optional Delay As Integer = 1000) As String
Function FTPDownload(Site, sUsername, sPassword, sLocalPath, sRemotePath, sRemoteFile, Optional Delay As Integer = 1000) As String
Public Function CountRowsInText(file_name As String) As Long
Public Function SplitTextFile(src As String, Optional des_fmt As String, Optional RowCntPerFile As Long = 65535, Optional file_idx_start As Integer = 0, Optional NumOfHdrRows As Long = 0, Optional DeleteSrc As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function DeleteRowInText(file_name As String, StartRow As Long, EndRow As Long) As String
Function ReplaceStrInFolder(folder_name As String, Arr_f As Variant, Arr_r As Variant, Optional StartRow As Long = 0) As String
Function ReplaceStrInFile(file_name As String, Arr_f As Variant, Arr_r As Variant, Optional StartRow As Long = 0) As String
Function WriteFile(ByVal File As String, ByVal content As String) As String    
Function ReadFile(ByVal File As String, Optional createFile As Boolean) As String
Function ReadFile_Truncate(ByVal File As String, Optional createFile As Boolean) As String
Function FileExists(file As String) As Boolean
Function GetFileUpdateTime(ByVal file As String) As Double
Private Sub ShowStudyForm()
Private Sub UserForm_Initialize()
Private Function IsPictureLoaded(ImageObject As Image) as Boolean
Public Function ArrayElement(arr As Variant, i1 As Variant, _
Public Function StringSplit(s As String, delim As String, Optional limit As Long = -1) As String()
Public Function StringJoin(arr() As Variant, delim As String) As String
Public Function NewLine() As String
' Returns an array suitable for using in an array formula.  When this function is called from an array formula, it will detect whether or not the array should be transposed to fit into the range.
Public Function GetArrayForFormula(arr As Variant) As Variant
Public Function RangeToArray(r As Range) As Variant()
' Returns the width of a column on a sheet.  If the column number is not given and this function is used in a formula, then it returns the column width of the cell containing the formula.
Public Function ColumnWidth(Optional c As Integer = 0) As Variant
' Returns the height of a row on a sheet.  If the row number is not given and this function is used in a formula, then it returns the row height of the cell containing the formula.
Public Function RowHeight(Optional r As Integer = 0) As Variant
Public Function GetFormula(r As Range, Optional r1c1 As Boolean = False) As Variant
'Evaluate an array function in VBA
Public Sub AppWait(Hrs As Double, Min As Double, Sec As Double)
Sub ExampleCode()
Private Sub SearchWithinDirectory()
Sub OpenWorkbook()
Sub DictBasics()
Public Function CoorTransform_Hk1980ToWgs84(Easting, Northing, Optional Delimiter As String = "") As Variant
Public Function CoorTransform_GridToGeographic(E0, N0, Lng0, Lat0, m_0, M0, a, e2, Easting, Northing, Optional accuracy = 6) As Variant
Public Function CoorTransform_Wgs84ToHK1980(Lng, Lat, Optional Delimiter As String = "") As Variant
Public Function CoorTransform_GeographicToGrid(E0, N0, Lng0, Lat0, m_0, M0, a, e2, Lng, Lat) As Variant
Public Sub DelTable(TableName As String)
'Delete Table by sub string
Public Sub DelTables_BySubStr(sub_str As String)
Public Function TableExist(TableName As String) As Boolean
Public Sub DelQuery(QueryName As String)
Public Function QueryExist(QueryName As String) As Boolean
Public Function Table_RecordCount(Tbl_name As String) As Long
Public Function Query_RecordCount(Qry_name As String) As Long
Public Function SQL_Obj_RecordCount(SQL_Obj_name As String) As Long
Public Function TableValid(TableName As String) As Boolean
Public Function QueryValid(Qryname As String) As Boolean
Public Function TransferObjSetInDb(TransferType As Variant, DatabaseType As String, DatabaseName As String, ObjectType As Variant, SrcList As Variant, DesList As Variant, Optional StructureOnly As Boolean = False, Optional StoreLogin As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function LinkTblSetInDailyFileInDir(DataDate As Date, DateFmt As String, DailyFileDir_path As String, DailyFile_prefix As String, FileFmt As String, SrcList As Variant, DesList As Variant, Optional ReferToLocal As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function LinkTblByTdf(Tbl_src_name As String, Tbl_des_name As String, str_conn As String) As String
Public Function RemoveLink() As String
Public Function GetLinkTblPath(Tbl_name As String) As String
Public Function GetLinkTblConnInfo(Tbl_name As String, param As String) As String
Public Function ObtainTblFldNameStr(Tbl_name As String)
Public Function FindColInTbl(Tbl_name As String, Col_name As String) As Integer
Public Function ExportTableToTxt(Tbl_name As String, des As String, Optional Delim As String = " ", Optional Quotation As String = "", Optional HasFldName As Boolean = True, Optional NullStr As String = "", Optional DateFmt As String = "MM/DD/YY", Optional TimeFmt As String = "h:mm") As String
Public Function ConvertTblToHtml(Tbl_name As String, Html As String) As String
Public Function ConcatRelated(strField As String, _
Public Function CompactAndRenewDb(Db_path As String) As String
Sub ExportStatsToExcel()
Private Sub processFolder(ByVal oParent As Outlook.MAPIFolder, ByVal wks As Worksheet)
Sub Test456()
Private Sub CommandCommands()
Private Sub SavePDFasTXT(FileName As String)
'*                  on a userform.  The PastePicture function takes an optional argument of
'*   CreatePicture  Private function to convert a bitmap or metafile handle to an OLE reference
'''Windows API Function Declarations
Private Declare Function IsClipboardFormatAvailable Lib "user32" (ByVal wFormat As Integer) As Long
Private Declare Function OpenClipboard Lib "user32" (ByVal hwnd As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function GetClipboardData Lib "user32" (ByVal wFormat As Integer) As Long
Private Declare Function CloseClipboard Lib "user32" () As Long
Private Declare Function OleCreatePictureIndirect Lib "olepro32.dll" (PicDesc As uPicDesc, RefIID As GUID, ByVal fPictureOwnsHandle As Long, IPic As IPicture) As Long
Declare Function CopyEnhMetaFile Lib "gdi32" Alias "CopyEnhMetaFileA" (ByVal hemfSrc As Long, ByVal lpszFile As String) As Long
Declare Function CopyImage Lib "user32" (ByVal handle As Long, ByVal un1 As Long, ByVal n1 As Long, ByVal n2 As Long, ByVal un2 As Long) As Long
Function PastePicture(Optional lXlPicType As Long = xlPicture) As IPicture
Private Function CreatePicture(ByVal hPic As Long, ByVal hPal As Long, ByVal lPicType) As IPicture
Private Function fnOLEError(lErrNum As Long) As String
'*                  on a userform.  The PastePicture function takes an optional argument of
'*   CreatePicture  Private function to convert a bitmap or metafile handle to an OLE reference
'''Windows API Function Declarations
Private Declare Function IsClipboardFormatAvailable Lib "user32" (ByVal wFormat As Integer) As Long
Private Declare Function OpenClipboard Lib "user32" (ByVal hwnd As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function GetClipboardData Lib "user32" (ByVal wFormat As Integer) As Long
Private Declare Function CloseClipboard Lib "user32" () As Long
Private Declare Function OleCreatePictureIndirect Lib "olepro32.dll" (PicDesc As uPicDesc, RefIID As GUID, ByVal fPictureOwnsHandle As Long, IPic As IPicture) As Long
Declare Function CopyEnhMetaFile Lib "gdi32" Alias "CopyEnhMetaFileA" (ByVal hemfSrc As Long, ByVal lpszFile As String) As Long
Declare Function CopyImage Lib "user32" (ByVal handle As Long, ByVal un1 As Long, ByVal n1 As Long, ByVal n2 As Long, ByVal un2 As Long) As Long
Sub test123()
Function SavePicture(Optional lXlPicType As Long = xlPicture) As Boolean
Private Function fnOLEError(lErrNum As Long) As String
Private Sub EachPivotTable()
Function PivotFillDown(TargetCell As Range)
Function TextExistsInPivot(SearchText As String, SheetName As String, PivTblName As String, PivFieldName As String) As Boolean
'       + Sub addLinks () : add an hyperlink to all the cells in the current selection. The URL will be the content of the cell
'       + Sub addLink (ByVal url As String, ByVal cell As Range) : add an hyperlink to cell given in argument to the URL given in argument. The URL will be the content of the cell
'       + Sub addLinks () : add an hyperlink to all the cells in the current selection. The URL will be the content of the cell
Sub addLinks()
'       + Sub addLink (ByVal url As String, ByVal cell As Range) : add an hyperlink to cell given in argument to the URL given in argument. The URL will be the content of the cell
Sub addLink(ByVal url As String, ByVal cell As Range)
Function getAddress(ByVal cell As Range)
Function selectXlDownRange(ByVal cell As Range) As Range
Function SheetExists(strWSName As String) As Boolean
Function FileExists(strFileFullPath As String) As Boolean
Function FolderExists(strFolderPath As String) As Boolean
Function GetFileName(strFilePath As String) As String
Function FindString(strFind As String) As Boolean
Function IsWbOpen(wbName As String) As Boolean
Function GetDate(Optional strDateFormat As String, Optional strDiversionFrom As String, Optional intDiversionValue As Integer) As String
Function Zip(strZipPath As String, strFilePath1 As String, Optional strZipFileName As String) As String
Function Mail( strTo As String, strSubject As String, strBody As String, Optional bSend As Boolean, Optional strCC As String, Optional strSignName As String, Optional strAttachPath1 As String, Optional strAttachPath2 As String, Optional strAttachPath3 As String, Optional strAttachPath4 As String, Optional strAttachPath5 As String)
Function BrowseForFile(Optional strWindowMsg As String) As String
Public Function BrowseForFolder(Optional Hwnd As Long = 0,Optional sTitle As String = "Please, select a folder", Optional BIF_Options As Integer,Optional vRootFolder As Variant) As String 
Function Copy(strSourceFullPath As String, strCopyToDestination As String) As String
Function PivotCacheRefresh() As Boolean
'@Description: Opens an url in the internet explorer. This function could be assigned to button.
Function OpenURL(strURL As String) As String
'@Description: Used to create a sheet that would be used by the function Log() where log information would be stored.
Function NewLog(Optional strSheetName As String) As Boolean
    'SheetExists function should be available within this module
' so this function is used depending on the programmer needs.
' Before the use of this function a new sheet should be created to store the logs. The NewLog() function could do this for you.
Function Log(strLogInfo As String, Optional strSheetName As String) As String
Sub TimeDebbugger()
            '| CALL A FUNCTION HERE |
Public Sub RunSQL_CmdWithoutWarning(SQL_cmd As String)
Public Function CreateSqlSeg_VectorColAgg(col_pattern As String, str_agg As String, Idx_start As Integer, Idx_end As Integer, Optional wildcard As String = "#") As String
Public Sub ModifyTbl_ReSelect(Tbl_name, str_select)
Public Function UpdateTblColBatchly(Tbl_src_name As String, Str_Col_Update As String, SQL_Format_Set As String, SQL_Format_Where As String) As String
Public Function UpdateTblCol(Tbl_src_name As String, ColName As String, SQL_Format_Set, SQL_Format_Where As String) As String
Public Function CreateTbl_ColAndExpr(Tbl_src_name As String, Str_Col_Id As String, Str_Col_Order As String, SQL_Seg_ColAndExpr As String, SQL_Seg_Where As String, Tbl_output_name As String) As String
'Create Table of group function, there is a default Group function for all columns, columns can be specified to different group fucntion
Public Function CreateTbl_Group(Tbl_input_name As String, Tbl_output_name As String, Str_Col_Group As String, Optional Str_GroupFunc_all As String = "", Optional GF_all_dbTypes As Variant = "", Optional Str_Col_UnSelected As String = "", Optional ByVal GroupFunc_Col_Pairs As Variant = "", Optional SQL_Seg_Where As String = "", Optional Str_Col_Order As String = "") As String
Public Function CreateTbls_Group(Tbl_MT_name As String) As String
Public Function CreateTbl_JoinTwoTbl(Tbl_src_1_name As String, Tbl_src_2_name As String, JoinCond As String, ColSet_Join_1 As Variant, ColSet_Join_2 As Variant, Tbl_des_name As String, Optional ColSet_src_1 As Variant = Null, Optional ColSet_src_2 As Variant = Null, Optional ColSet_Order As Variant = Null) As String
Public Function CreateTbl_ConcatTbls(Tbl_src_Set As Variant, Tbl_des_name As String, Optional Type_Set As Variant = "") As String
Public Function ExecuteSQLiteCmdSet(SQLiteDb_path As String, CmdSet As String) As String
Public Function AppendTblToSQLite(Tbl_src_name As String, Tbl_des_name As String) As String
Function SuperSubV(strOldText As String, ByVal Rng1 As Range, ByVal rng2 As Range) As String
Function SuperSubH(strOldText As String, ByVal Rng1 As Range, ByVal rng2 As Range) As String
Function SheetExists(strWSName As String) As Boolean
Function folderExists(strFolderPath As String) As Boolean
' because the function would catch the string after the last slash "/" or "\".
Function GetFileName(strFilePath As String) As String
Function IsWbOpen(wbName As String) As Boolean
Function FindString(strFind As String) As Boolean
    '@Param strZipFileName: Optional String. Name of the Zip. If this param is empty the function will apply as a name the name of the file that should be zipped.
Function Zip(strZipPath As String, strFilePath1 As String, Optional strZipFileName As String) As String
    arryFiles = Array(strFilePath1) 'You can add additional param strFilePath2 as function input and add it to the array so it would zip two files...
'Note: Please note when you set "True" to the 4th argument the function will use your outlook to send directly the email.
Function Mail( _
Function BrowseForFile(Optional strWindowMsg As String) As String
Public Function BrowseForFolder( _
'This function has been added to the lib because my everyday automated excel reports had to be renamed with a different date and format.
Function GetDate(Optional strDateFormat As String, Optional strDiversionFrom As String, Optional intDiversionValue As Integer) As String
Function Copy(strSourceFullPath As String, strCopyToDestination As String) As String
'I am using this function on Workbook_Open() when a pivot contains cached items from some outdated data.
Function PivotCacheRefresh() As Boolean
'@Description: Opens an url in the internet explorer. This function could be assigned to button.
Function OpenURL(strURL As String) As String
'@Description: Used to create a sheet that would be used by the function Log() where log information would be stored.
Function NewLog(Optional strSheetName As String) As Boolean
    'SheetExists function should be available within this module
' so this function is used depending on the programmer needs.
' Before the use of this function a new sheet should be created to store the logs. The NewLog() function could do this for you.
Function Log(strLogInfo As String, Optional strSheetName As String) As String
Private Sub MainText()
Private Sub SetupTweet()
Private Sub AllInternalPasswords()
    '   eliminate one Exit Sub (Version 1.1.1)
Public Function ModuleExists(moduleName As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As Boolean
Public Sub RemoveModule(moduleName As String, Optional wb As Workbook)
Public Sub ExportModule(moduleName As String, moduleFilename As String, Optional wb As Workbook)
Public Function ImportModule(moduleFilename As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As VBComponent
Declare Function GetUserName Lib "advapi32.dll" Alias "GetUserNameA" _
Public Function GetLogonName() As String
'       + Function writeFile (ByVal file As String, ByVal content As String) As String : overwrite the content specified in the file specified.
'       + Function getCurrentWorkbookPath() As String
Function getCurrentWorkbookPath()
'       + Function moveSheetsInCurrentWorkbook(ByVal wkFullPath As String, Optional ByVal namePattern As String) As String
'           - Emile Fyon        02/09/2012      Revision in order to make the function ActiveCell-free
Sub moveSheetsInCurrentWorkbook(ByVal wkFullPath As String, Optional ByVal namePattern As String)
Function getSheetNameRedo(ByVal pattern As String, ByVal ws As Worksheet, ByVal wk As Workbook) As String
Sub getReplacementPatterns()
'       + Function listSheets() As String
'           - Emile Fyon        02/09/2012      Revision in order to make the function ActiveCell-free
Sub listSheets(Optional ByVal destRg As Range)
Sub copySheets()
Sub renameSheets()
Sub concatenateSheets()
'       + Function getCurrentWorkbookPath() As String
Function getSheetName(ByVal cell As Range)
Sub extractPivot()
Sub extractChart(ByVal ws As Worksheet, ByVal wsExtract As Worksheet, ByVal rgExtract As Range)
Public Function Dict_CreateEmpty() As Variant
Public Function Dict_AddOrUpdate(ThisDict As Variant, Key As String, Value As Variant) As Variant
Public Function Coll_ReturnUniqueCollFromColl(FullCollection As Collection) As Variant
Public Function Coll_ReturnStringListFromCollection(FullCollection As Collection) As Variant
Public Function Coll_ToArray(FullCollection As Collection) As Variant
Public Function Coll_ExistsInCollection(SearchString As String, Coll As Collection) As Boolean
Public Function Coll_AddIfUnique(Addition As String, Coll As Collection)
Public Function Coll_Sort(ByVal c As Collection) As Collection
Private Sub Heapify(ByVal c As Collection, Index() As Long, ByVal i1 As Long, ByVal n As Long)
Private Sub Exchange(Index() As Long, ByVal i As Long, ByVal j As Long)
'Public Function ExportVBComponent(VBComp As vbide.VBComponent, _
'    ' ExportVBComponent   - This function exports the code module of a VBComponent to a text
'Public Function GetVBAFileExtension(VBComp As vbide.VBComponent) As String
Sub Test()
Function FileWriteBinary(vData As Variant, sFileName As String, Optional bAppendToFile As Boolean = True) As Boolean
Function FileReadBinary(sFileName As String) As Variant
Private Declare Sub CopyMemory Lib "kernel32" Alias "RtlMoveMemory" (dest As Any, source As Any, ByVal bytes As Long)
Public Function ArrayRank(arr As Variant) As Integer
    If (vType And vbArray) = 0 Then Exit Function 'if not an array
Public Function ArrayLen(arr As Variant, Optional nDim As Integer = 1) As Long
Public Function ArrayIndexOf(arr As Variant, val As Variant) As Long
Public Function ArrayContains(arr As Variant, val As Variant) As Boolean
Public Function ArraySubset(arr() As Variant, Optional r1 As Long = -1, Optional r2 As Long = -1, Optional c1 As Long = -1, Optional c2 As Long = -1) As Variant()
Public Function NormalizeArray(arr As Variant) As Variant
    ' Returns a single-dimension array with lower bound 1, if given a one-dimensional array with any lower bound or a two-dimensional array with one dimension having only one element.  This function will always return a copy of the given array.
Public Function GetUniqueItems(arr() As Variant) As Variant()
Private Sub QuickSort(vArray() As Variant, inLow As Long, inHi As Long)
Public Function SortArray(arr() As Variant) As Variant()
Public Sub SortArrayInPlace(arr() As Variant)
Public Function GetItemInArray(Array_src As Variant, idx As Long) As Variant
Public Function GetItemInStrArray(StrArray_src As String, separator As String, idx As Long) As Variant
Public Function FindItemInArray(Array_src As Variant, item As String) As Long
Public Function AppendArray(Array_src As Variant, Array_append As Variant) As String
Public Sub DeleteArrayItem(arr As Variant, index As Long)
Public Function GetUsedRangeOnSheet(Optional thisSheet As Worksheet = Nothing) As Range
    'I've found Excel's builtin "usedRange" function to be unreliable at times. This is a highly usable replacement for data-oriented sheets
Public Function GetLastUsedRowOnSheet(Optional thisSheet As Worksheet = Nothing) As Long
Public Function GetLastUsedColumnOnSheet(Optional thisSheet As Worksheet = Nothing) As Long
Public Function InString(stringToSearch As String, stringToLookFor As String, Optional startingAt As Long = 1, Optional compareMethod As VbCompareMethod = vbBinaryCompare) As Boolean
    'Helper function for checking if a string is within another string and returns a boolean.
Public Function SheetExists(ByVal sheetName As String) As Boolean
    'Convenience function for checking if a given sheet exists.
Public Function FolderExists(strPath As String) As Boolean
Public Function FileExists(FileName As String) As Boolean
Public Function GetQuarter(Optional Offset As Long = 0, Optional ByVal DateSeed As Date = vbNull, Optional ErrorLog As BM_ErrorLog = Nothing) As String
Public Function GetFiscalYear(Optional Offset As Long = 0, Optional ByVal DateSeed As Date = vbNull) As String
Public Function GetLastCompleteQuarter(Optional ByVal DateSeed As Date = vbNull) As Long
Public Function GetFirstMonthOfQuarter(Optional ByVal DateSeed As Date = vbNull) As Long
Public Function GetStartOfYearOffset(Optional DateSeed As Date = vbNull) As Long
Public Function GetActualsOfYearOffset(Optional DateSeed As Date = vbNull) As Long
Public Function CreatePivotTableOnSheet(ws As Worksheet, dataSheet As Worksheet, Optional atCell As String = "A1") As PivotTable
    'Convenience function for creating a pivot table from a selected data sheet at a specified location
Public Function ReadTextFile(Fname As String, Length As Integer) As Variant
Public Function StripDateFromSheetName(thisSheet As Worksheet) As String
    'Helper function for striping dates from sheets named in the format "SheetName 2-18" where "2-18" represents a date. For reports generated automatically from code.
Private Function PromptForMultipleTextInputs() As Variant
Private Function Read2DExceptionList(fileName) As Dictionary
Private Function OpenPipeSeparatedUTF8() As Workbook
Private Sub ReSaveWorkbookAsXlsx(thisWorkbook As Workbook)
Public Sub FreezePanesOnSheet(sheetToFreeze As Worksheet, atPosition As Range)
    'Helper function to freeze panes on a sheet. Leaves handling of screen updating to the user
Public Sub AddConditionalFormattingForUndefinedOnSheet(sheetToFormat As Worksheet)
Public Sub InitializeColumnHeadersFor(sheetToInitialize As Worksheet, outputDictionary As Dictionary, Optional ByVal headerRow As Long = 1)
    'ToDo: re-write Sub to Function for clearer semantics... however passing the outputDictionary to the Sub initializes it for the user...    
Private Declare Function CallNamedPipe Lib "kernel32" Alias "CallNamedPipeA" (ByVal lpNamedPipeName As String, ByVal lpInBuffer As Any, ByVal nInBufferSize As Long, ByRef lpOutBuffer As Any, ByVal nOutBufferSize As Long, ByRef lpBytesRead As Long, ByVal nTimeOut As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function GetCurrentProcessId Lib "kernel32" () As Long
Public Function IsWorkbookOpen(wbFilename As String) As Boolean
    ' Determines whether a given workbook has been opened.  Pass this function a filename only, not a full path.
Public Function ChartExists(chartName As String, Optional sheetName As String = vbNullString, Optional wb As Workbook) As Boolean
Public Function SheetExists(sheetName As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As Boolean
Public Function WorkSheetExist(oWb As Workbook, SheetName As String) As Boolean
Public Sub DeleteSheetByName(sheetName As String, Optional wb As Workbook)
Public Sub DeleteSheet(s As Worksheet)
Public Sub DeleteSheets(s As Sheets)
Private Sub DeleteSheetOrSheets(s As Object)
Public Function CellReference(ByVal r As Long, ByVal c As Integer, Optional sheet As String = "", Optional absoluteRow As Boolean = False, Optional absoluteCol As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function GetRealUsedRange(s As Worksheet, Optional fromTopLeft As Boolean = True) As Range
Public Function SetValueIfNeeded(rng As Range, val As Variant) As Boolean
Public Function ExcelCol(c As Integer) As String
Public Function ExcelColNum(c As String) As Integer
Private Function ExcelCol_ZeroBased(c As Integer) As String
Public Function ExcelErrorType(e As Variant) As String
Public Sub ShowStatusMessage(statusMessage As String)
Public Sub FlashStatusMessage(statusMessage As String)
Public Sub ClearStatusMessage()
Public Sub SendMessageToListener(msg As String)
Public Function GetExcelTable(tblName As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As VBALib_ExcelTable
Public Function GetExcelLink(linkFilename As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As VBALib_ExcelLink
Public Function GetWorkbookFileFormat(fileExtension As String) As XlFileFormat
Public Function SaveWorkbookAs(wb As Workbook, newFilename As String, Optional oAction As OverwriteAction = oaPrompt, Optional openReadOnly As Boolean = False) As Boolean
Public Function SaveActiveWorkbookAs(newFilename As String, Optional oAction As OverwriteAction = oaPrompt, Optional openReadOnly As Boolean = False) As Boolean
Public Function GetCornerCell(r As Range, c As Corner) As Range
Public Function GetAllExcelLinks(Optional wb As Workbook) As Variant
Private Function GetMatchingLinkName(linkFilename As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As String
Public Function ExcelLinkExists(linkFilename As String, Optional wb As Workbook) As Boolean
Public Sub RefreshAccessConnections(Optional wb As Workbook)
Public Function AppendSqlObjToAndActivateWs(oWs As Worksheet, SqlObj_name As String, Optional AddBorder As Boolean = False) As String
Public Function ReplaceStrInWsRng(oWsRng As Range, What As Variant, Replacement As Variant, Optional LookAt As Variant, Optional SearchOrder As Variant, Optional MatchCase As Variant, Optional MatchByte As Variant, Optional SearchFormat As Variant, Optional ReplaceFormat As Variant) As String
Public Function LinkToWorksheetInWorkbook(Wb_path As String, ByVal SheetNameList As Variant, Optional ByVal SheetNameLocalList As Variant, Optional ByVal ShtSeriesList As Variant, Optional HasFieldNames As Boolean = True) As String
Public Function ExportTblToSht(Wb_path, Tbl_name As String, sht_name As String) As String
        ' Tbl_LookupReturn    - Used with Function Tbl_Lookup
Public Function WB_OpenOrSelect(WBDir As String, WBName As String) As Variant
Public Function WB_IsOpen(WBName As String) As Boolean
Public Function ColumnLetter(ColumnNumber As Variant) As Variant
        '                 Tested 3/25/11 - significantly quicker than function ColumnLetter2; validated same results either way
Public Function Picture_AddFromFile(FN As String, ImageName As String, _
Public Function Comment_AddPicture(CommentCell As Range, _
Public Function Comment_AddText(CommentCell As Range, _
Public Function Validation_DoesItExist(cellRange As Range) As Boolean
Public Function Validation_AddList(RangeToAddValidation As Range, _
Public Function Validiation_DeleteAll(cellRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Validation_WholeNumber(cellRange As Range, _
Public Function Validation_FreeText(cellRange As Range, _
Public Function Borders_AddStandard(TableRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Borders_AddDblOutside(TableRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function NamedRange_Add(NamedRange As Range, _
Public Function NamedRange_AddValueIfUnqiue(Value As String, _
Public Function NamedRange_Replace(NamedRangeName As String, ReplaceCollection As Collection) As Boolean
Public Function Hyperlink_Add(AnchorRange As Range, _
Public Function ListBox_ReturnSelected(List_Box_OLE_Object As Variant) As Variant
    ' Example function call:
Public Function EmbededObject_Add(FullFileName As String, _
Public Function EmbededObject_ClearAllInWB() As Variant
Public Function Tbl_Lookup(Tbl As Range, _
        '   EXAMPLE FUNCTION CALLS:
Public Function Tbl_ReturnUniqueList(SearchRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Tbl_GetHeaderColumn(SearchField As String, _
Public Function ExtTbl(Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtDown(Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtRight(Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtDownNonBlank(Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtTblNonBlank(Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtAllTbl(ByRef Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtAllDown(ByRef Rng As Range, _
Public Function ExtAllRight(ByRef Rng As Range, _
Private Function LastRow(ByVal OfSheet As Worksheet, Optional ByVal InColumn As Long = 0) As Long
Private Function LastColumn(ByVal OfSheet As Worksheet, Optional ByVal InRow As Long = 0) As Integer
Public Function Range_Set(WSName As String, LowCol As Variant, LowRow As Variant, Optional HighCol As Variant, Optional HighRow As Variant) As Variant
Public Function Range_CopyPasteValues(CopyRange As Range, PasteRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Range_CopyPasteAll(CopyRange As Range, PasteRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Range_Sort(wsRange As Range, RangeIncludesHeader As Boolean) As Variant
Public Function Range_GetMaxRow(FirstCellInRange As Range) As Variant
    Debug.Print "Error in Function Range_GetMaxRow: " & Err.Number & ": " & Err.Description
Public Function Range_ConvertTo1DArray(InputRange As Range) As Variant
Private Function Range_ConvertToArray(InputRange As Range) As Variant
Public Function Range_FindMatch(SearchString As String, SearchRange As Range) As Variant
Private Function DoesFileExist(FN As String) As Variant
        Debug.Print "Error in Private Function DoesFileExist: " & Err.Number & ": " & Err.Description
Public Function ErrorTrap_WSExists(WSName As String) As Boolean
Public Function ErrorTrap_ChartExists(ChartName As String) As Boolean
Private Declare Function GetTempPathA Lib "kernel32" (ByVal nBufferLength As Long, ByVal lpBuffer As String) As Long
Public Function FileExists(ByVal testFilename As String, Optional findFolders As Boolean = False) As Boolean
    'Determines whether a file with the given name exists. @param findFolders: If true, the function will return true if a folder with the given name exists.
Public Function FolderExists(folderName As String) As Boolean
Public Function GetDirectoryName(ByVal p As String) As String
Public Function GetFilename(ByVal p As String) As String
Public Function GetFileExtension(ByVal p As String) As String
Public Function ListFiles(filePattern As String) As Variant()
Public Function ListFolders(folderPattern As String) As Variant()
Public Function GetTempPath() As String
Private Function ListFiles_Internal(filePattern As String, attrs As Long) As Variant()
Public Function CombinePaths(p1 As String, p2 As String) As String
Public Function NormalizePath(ByVal p As String) As String
Public Sub MkDirRecursive(folderName As String)
Private Sub MkDirRecursiveInternal(folderName As String, originalFolderName As String)
    ' Too many recursive calls to this function (GetDirectoryName will eventually return an empty string)
Public Sub ListFiles(ByVal strPath As String, ByVal cellDestination As Range)
Function CheckFolder(ByVal strPath As String) As String
Function FolderExists(ByVal fullPath As String) As String
Function CreateDirs(ByVal fullPath As String) As String
Function CreateFolder(ByVal fullPath As String) As Boolean
Sub ListFolder(sFolderPath As String, ByVal cellDestination As Range)
Sub TestListFolders()
Sub listFoldersFullInfo(SourceFolderName As String, IncludeSubfolders As Boolean)
Function GetOldestFileInDir(ByVal path As String, ByVal fileNameMask As String) As Date
Public Sub WrapIfError()
Public Sub FormulasToValues()
Public Sub TextToNumber()
Public Sub TogglePageBreaks()
Public Sub KillStyles()
        "Delete?", vbInformation + vbYesNo) <> vbYes Then Exit Sub 'Get Confirmation
Public Function Show_MsgBox(str As String) As Boolean
Public Function Enable_MsgBox()
Public Function Disable_MsgBox()
Public Sub Excel_On()
Public Sub Excel_Off()
Public Sub Excel_Toggle()
Public Sub PasswordBreaker()
Public Function SQLsqueezer(sqlString As String, serverAddress As String, Optional userID As String = vbNullString, Optional password As String = vbNullString, Optional database As String = vbNullString, Optional shouldReturnResultsAtRange As Range = Nothing, Optional shouldReturnListArray As Boolean = True, Optional shouldReturnHeadersAtTopOfRange As Boolean = True) As Variant
Public Declare Function ShellExecute Lib "shell32.dll" Alias "ShellExecuteA" (ByVal hwnd As Long, ByVal lpOperation As String, ByVal lpFile As String, ByVal lpParameters As String, ByVal lpDirectory As String, ByVal nShowCmd As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function OpenProcess Lib "kernel32.dll" (ByVal dwDesiredAccessas As Long, ByVal bInheritHandle As Long, ByVal dwProcId As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function CloseHandle Lib "kernel32.dll" (ByVal hObject As Long) As Long
Public Function CommitToGIT(OutputDir As String) As Boolean
Private Sub OpenAnyFileUsingDefaultProgram(FullFileName As String)
Private Function IsProcessOpen(PID As Long) As Boolean
Public Function Min(X As Double, Y As Double) As Double
Public Function Max(X As Double, Y As Double) As Double 
Public Function Log10(X As Double) As Double
Public Function Ceil(X As Double) As Double
Public Function Ceiling(num As Double, Optional significance As Double = 1, Optional places As Integer = 0) As Double
Public Function Floor(num As Double, Optional significance As Double = 1, Optional places As Integer = 0) As Double
Private Sub ValidateFloorCeilingParams(ByRef significance As Double, ByRef places As Integer)
Function SheetExists(sWSName as String) As Boolean
Function FileExists(sFileFullPath as String) As Boolean
Function FolderExists(sFolderPath as String) As Boolean
Function GetFileName(sFilePath as String) As String
Function IsWbOpen(wbName as String) As Boolean
Function FindString(sFind as String) As Boolean
Function Zip(sZipPath as String, sFilePath1 as String, Optional sZipFileName as String) As String
    arrFiles = Array(sFilePath1) 'add sFilePath2 to function & here to append more, or build loop or whatever
Function BrowseFile(Optional sWinMsg as String) As String
Function BrowseFolder(Optional Hwnd as Long=0,Optional sTitle as String="Please select folder.",Optional BIF_Options as Integer,Optional vRootFolder as Variant) As String
Function GetDate(Optional sDateFormat As String, Optional sDiversionFrom As String, Optional iDiversionValue As Integer) As String
Function FileCopy(sSrcFullPath As String, sDestFullPath As String) As String
Function PivotCacheRefresh() As Boolean
Function OpenURL(sURL As String) As String
Function NewLog(Optional sShtName As String) As Boolean
Function Log(sLogInfo As String, Optional sShtName As String) As String
Function NumberToPrint(Number As Variant, ReturnType As NumberPrintReturnType, ShowCommas As Boolean) As Variant
Function LogX(Number As Double, Optional Base As Double = 10) As Variant
Function Log10(Number As Double) As Variant
Function StudentTText_UnequalVar(ByVal ControlMean As Double, ByVal ControlSD As Double, ByVal ControlN As Integer, ByVal DoseMean As Double, ByVal DoseSD As Double, ByVal DoseN As Integer) As Double
Function StudentTText_EqualVar(ByVal ControlMean As Double, ByVal ControlSD As Double, ByVal ControlN As Integer, ByVal DoseMean As Double, ByVal DoseSD As Double, ByVal DoseN As Integer) As Double
Function FishersExactText(ByVal A1 As Long, ByVal B1 As Long, ByVal A2 As Long, ByVal B2 As Long) As Variant
Function LogXFactorial(ByVal Value As Long, Optional Base As Integer = 10) As Variant
Public Function LinInterpolate(XValue As Range, XRange As Range, YRange As Range) As Variant
Function SigFig(Value As Double, SigFigs As Integer) As String
Public Function RegExM(ByVal Pattern As String, ByVal SourceString As String, Optional ByVal IgnoreCase As Boolean = False, Optional ByVal Glbl As Boolean = True, Optional ByVal Multiline As Boolean = False) As MatchCollection
Public Function RegExR(ByVal Pattern As String, ByVal Replacement As String, ByVal SourceString As String, Optional ByVal IgnoreCase As Boolean = False, Optional ByVal Glbl As Boolean = True, Optional ByVal Multiline As Boolean = False) As String
Private Sub RegExDemo()
Function stripTags(ByVal txt As String) As String
Function FileNameFromFullPath(ByVal txt As String) As String
Function matchExpreg(ByVal txt As String, ByVal matchPattern As String, ByVal replacePattern As String) As String
Function findExpreg(ByVal txt As String, ByVal matchPattern As String) As String
Private Declare Function GetExitCodeProcess Lib "kernel32" (ByVal hProcess As Long, lpExitCode As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function WaitForSingleObject Lib "kernel32" (ByVal hHandle As Long, ByVal dwMilliseconds As Long) As Long
Declare Function OpenProcess Lib "kernel32" (ByVal dwDesiredAccess As Long, ByVal bInheritHandle As Long, ByVal dwProcessId As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function CloseHandle Lib "kernel32" (ByVal hObject As Long) As Long
Private Declare Function FormatMessage Lib "kernel32" Alias "FormatMessageA" (ByVal dwFlags As Long, lpSource As Any, ByVal dwMessageId As Long, ByVal dwLanguageId As Long, ByVal lpBuffer As String, ByVal nSize As Long, Arguments As Long) As Long
Declare Sub Sleep Lib "kernel32" (ByVal dwMilliseconds As Long)
Declare Function GlobalFindAtomA Lib "kernel32" (ByVal lpstr As String) As Integer
Declare Function GlobalAddAtomA Lib "kernel32" (ByVal lpstr As String) As Integer
Declare Function GlobalFindAtomW Lib "kernel32" (ByVal lpstr As String) As Integer
Declare Function GlobalAddAtomW Lib "kernel32" (ByVal lpstr As String) As Integer
Declare Function FindWindowA Lib "user32" (ByVal lpClassName As String, ByVal lpWindowName As String) As Long
Declare Function IsWindow Lib "user32" (ByVal hwnd As Long) As Long
Public Function ShellAndWait(ByVal cmd As String, ByVal window_style As VbAppWinStyle) As Boolean
Public Function Shell_SendKeysWithTimeout(oshell As Object, CmdTxt As String, Timeout As Integer) As String
Public Sub RunAndKill()
Private Function IsProcessOpen(PID As Long) As Boolean
Public Sub OpenAnyFile(FullFileName as String)
Public Function RegExM(ByVal Pattern As String, ByVal Source As String, Optional ByVal IgnoreCase As Boolean=False,Optional ByVal MultiLine As Boolean=False,Optional ByVal Globle As Boolean=False) As String
Public Function RegExR(ByVal Pattern As String,ByVal Replace As String,ByVal Souce As String,Optional ByVal IgnoreCase As Boolean=False,Optional ByVal MultiLine As Boolean=False,Optional ByVal Globle As Boolean=True) As String
Public Function SplitTrim(s As String, delim As String) As String()
Public Function SplitText(InTextLine As String, Delimeter As String) As Variant
Public Function SplitTextReturn(InTextLine As String, Delimeter As String, ReturnID As Integer) As String
Function SplitTextReturnOne(InputString As String, ReturnValue As Integer) As String
Public Function ReturnTextBetween(SearchText As String, StartField As String, EndField As String) As String
Public Function IsTextFound(ByVal FindText As String, ByVal WithinText As String) As Boolean
Function Printf(ByVal FormatWithPercentSign As String, ParamArray InsertArray()) As String
Public Function TrimChars(s As String, toTrim As String)
Public Function TrimLeadingChars(s As String, toTrim As String)
Public Function TrimTrailingChars(s As String, toTrim As String)
Public Function BegWith(s As String, prefix As String, Optional caseSensitive As Boolean=True) As Boolean
Public Function EndWith(s As String, suffix As String, Optional caseSensitive As Boolean=True) As Boolean
Function ScrubFileName(stringToScrub As String) As String
Function ScrubCharReturns(ByVal txt As String) As String
Function ScrubSqlString(text As String, Optional ByVal isNumber As Boolean) As String
Public Function AddNewLine(Optional Repeat As Integer=1) As String
Public Function AddQuotes(ByVal TextInQuotes As String) As String
Public Function AddTab(Optional Repeat As Integer=1) As String
Public Function AddToArrayIfUnique(ByVal NewString As String, ArrayName() As Variant) As Variant
Public Function SplitStrIntoArray(str As String, separator As String) As Variant
Public Function FindStrInArray(Array_str As Variant, str As String) As Integer
Public Function BuildXMLText(ByVal FieldName As String, ByVal Value As String, Optional NumTabs As Integer=0) As String